<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Cassie Moy</title>
    <link>/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Cassie Moy</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 01 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Resume</title>
      <link>/posts/resume/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/resume/</guid>
      <description> </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Circle with centered text in HTML and CSS</title>
      <link>/posts/circle-with-centered-text/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 25 Aug 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/circle-with-centered-text/</guid>
      <description>As we learned with the box model, browsers basically represent everything in boxes, or rectangles. Fortunately, you can think of a circle as a square with really rounded corners.
We can make a square from a div by setting its height and width properties to the same value.
Then, we need to set the border-radius property, which controls the roundness of an element&amp;rsquo;s corners.
Lastly, we can use flexbox to help us center the text by setting the div&amp;rsquo;s display property to flex.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About this site</title>
      <link>/posts/about-this-site/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 11 Feb 2018 22:40:57 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/about-this-site/</guid>
      <description>This site is built with Hugo, with a little help from Minimal to get up and running. The 💻 ✨ on the landing page is provided by EmojiOne.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ask me</title>
      <link>/posts/ask-me/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Feb 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/ask-me/</guid>
      <description>Hi there! 👋
If you&amp;rsquo;re trying to get into tech and you belong to an under-represented group1, if you want help, I want to help. You can reach out to me via email at hello@cassie.nyc, or DM me on Twitter @cassie_moy.
You can ask me to:
 Proofread or give feedback on your resume/portfolio/LinkedIn profile Introduce you to someone I know, if we know each other Help practice behavioral interviews, especially if you&amp;rsquo;re telling the story of why you&amp;rsquo;re trying to get into tech if you&amp;rsquo;re coming from a non-traditional background Talk through bootcamps critically, or talk through what might happen next after graduating from one Be a Meetup buddy so that you&amp;rsquo;re not going to tech events alone, if you&amp;rsquo;re in NYC   1.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>